degreeholder.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is intended to transparently disclose our methods of data collection and illustrate our ongoing commitment to ensuring your privacy. 

**Data Log and Server Storage**

Activity on DegreeHolder.com will be instantaneously and automatically recorded by our server to track site activity, gauge company performance and analyze potential problems. Personal information cannot be extracted from this data anywhere offsite as all stored data is encrypted. 

**Data Collection and Usage**

Requesting information from one of our application pages requires a potential enrollee to submit a form that includes information specific to them as an individual such as name, phone number, address, and email address. This data is unique and specific to each individual applicant. The information collected on our site will only be sent to the institution that the potential applicant is requesting information from and/or its authorized agent. 

**Partners and Banners**

DegreeHolder.com contains links to other sites and some of these sites may contain their own application pages and have their own data collection and distribution policies. While we make every effort to only link to responsible and trust worthy sites, please be aware that DegreeHolder.com in no way takes responsibility for actions which these third party sites might employ. 

**Cookies**

As a matter of policy, DegreeHolder.com does not collect personal information using cookies. 

For questions regarding this privacy statement or other company policies, please feel free to contact us.
